<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Free on VickyLai.com</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.com/tags/free/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Free on VickyLai.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 13:12:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vickylai.com/tags/free/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adorable bookmarklets want to help delete your social media data</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/adorable-bookmarklets-want-to-help-delete-your-social-media-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 13:12:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/adorable-bookmarklets-want-to-help-delete-your-social-media-data/</guid>
      <description>A little while ago I wrote about a Lambda function I called ephemeral for deleting my old tweets. While it&amp;rsquo;s a great project for someone familiar with or wanting to learn to use Lambda, it isn&amp;rsquo;t simple for a non-technical person to set up. There are services out there that will delete your tweets for you, but require your access credentials. There didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be anything that provided convenience without also requiring authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m automatically deleting my old tweets using AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/why-im-automatically-deleting-my-old-tweets-using-aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 10:51:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/why-im-automatically-deleting-my-old-tweets-using-aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>From now on, my tweets are ephemeral. Here’s why I’m deleting all my old tweets, and the AWS Lambda function I’m using to do all this for free.
Click here to skip to the code part.
Stuff and opinions I&amp;rsquo;ve only been a one-bag nomad for a little over a year and a half. Before that, I lived as most people do in an apartment or a house. I owned furniture, more clothing than I strictly needed, and enough &amp;ldquo;stuff&amp;rdquo; to fill at least a few moving boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running a free Twitter bot on AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/running-a-free-twitter-bot-on-aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 10:29:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/running-a-free-twitter-bot-on-aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>If you read About time, you&amp;rsquo;ll know that I&amp;rsquo;m a big believer in spending time now on building things that save time in the future. To this end I built a simple Twitter bot in Go that would occasionally post links to my articles and keep my account interesting even when I&amp;rsquo;m too busy to use it. The tweets help drive traffic to my sites, and I don&amp;rsquo;t have to lift a finger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting your static site with AWS S3, Route 53, and CloudFront</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/hosting-your-static-site-with-aws-s3-route-53-and-cloudfront/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 20:46:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/hosting-your-static-site-with-aws-s3-route-53-and-cloudfront/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago I decided to stop freeloading on GitHub pages and move one of my sites to Amazon Web Services (AWS). It turns out that I&amp;rsquo;m still mostly freeloading (yay free tier) so it amounted to a learning experience. Here are the components that let me host and serve the site at my custom domain with HTTPS.
 Static site in Amazon Web Services S3 bucket Route 53 handling the DNS CloudFront for distribution and a custom SSL certificate  I set all that up most of a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top free resources for developing coding superpowers</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/top-free-resources-for-developing-coding-superpowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 08:14:09 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/top-free-resources-for-developing-coding-superpowers/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m frequently asked for my opinion on how to get started on being a freelance developer. If you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to live the life of a remote working digital nomad, whichever career you choose, having a little coding expertise in your back pocket will be a big benefit.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick list of resources that you should definitely look at first if you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to gain some coding superpowers for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I ditched WordPress and set up my custom domain HTTPS site for (almost) free</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-ditched-wordpress-and-set-up-my-custom-domain-https-site-for-almost-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 13:16:17 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-ditched-wordpress-and-set-up-my-custom-domain-https-site-for-almost-free/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got annoyed with WordPress.com. While using the service has its pros (like https and a mobile responsive website, and being very visual and beginner-friendly) it&amp;rsquo;s limiting. For someone who&amp;rsquo;s comfortable enough to be tweaking CSS but who&amp;rsquo;s not interested in creating their own theme (or paying upwards of $50 for one), I felt I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really the type of consumer WordPress.com was suited to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>