<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frontend on VickyLai.io</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.io/tags/frontend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Frontend on VickyLai.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 14:05:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vickylai.io/tags/frontend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Time</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/about-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 14:05:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/about-time/</guid>
      <description>This morning I read an article that&amp;rsquo;s been making the rounds lately: Modern Media Is a DoS Attack on Your Free Will.
It&amp;rsquo;s made me think, which I must admit, I at first didn&amp;rsquo;t like. See, when I wake up in the morning (and subsequently wake up my computer) the first thing I do is go on Twitter to catch up on everything I missed while I was asleep. All this before my first coffee, mind you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top free resources for developing coding superpowers</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-resources-for-coding-superpowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 08:14:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-resources-for-coding-superpowers/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m frequently asked for my opinion on how to get started on being a freelance developer. If you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to live the life of a remote working digital nomad, whichever career you choose, having a little coding expertise in your back pocket will be a big benefit.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick list of resources that you should definitely look at first if you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to gain some coding superpowers for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I ditched WordPress and set up my custom domain HTTPS site for (almost) free</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-custom-domain-website-https/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 13:16:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-custom-domain-website-https/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got annoyed with WordPress.com. While using the service has its pros (like https and a mobile responsive website, and being very visual and beginner-friendly) it&amp;rsquo;s limiting. For someone who&amp;rsquo;s comfortable enough to be tweaking CSS but who&amp;rsquo;s not interested in creating their own theme (or paying upwards of $50 for one), I felt I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really the type of consumer WordPress.com was suited to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>