<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vicky Lai on VickyLai.com</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vicky Lai on VickyLai.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 19:27:28 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://vickylai.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Git commit practices your future self will thank you for
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/git-commit-practices-your-future-self-will-thank-you-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 08:54:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/git-commit-practices-your-future-self-will-thank-you-for/</guid>
      <description>A history of clean commits can be evidence of a lot of things: attention to detail, good work ethic, and genuine investment in the project. What do your Git commits say about you?
If, like me, there might be one or two less than stellar ones, well, we’re only human. A nice part of being human is having the ability to learn new and complex things fairly quickly, and continuously improve ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            An automatic interactive pre-commit checklist, in the style of infomercials
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/interactive-pre-commit-hook-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 09:38:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/interactive-pre-commit-hook-checklist/</guid>
      <description>What’s that, you say? You’ve become tired of regular old boring paper checklists? Well, my friend, today is your lucky day! You, yes, you, can become the proud owner of a brand-spanking-new automatic interactive pre-commit hook checklist! You’re gonna love this! Your life will be so much easier! Just wait until your friends see you.
What’s a pre-commit hook? Did you know that nearly 1 out of 5 coders are too embarrassed to ask this question?</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            How to set up a short feedback loop as a solo coder
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-to-set-up-a-short-feedback-loop-as-a-solo-coder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 10:08:41 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-to-set-up-a-short-feedback-loop-as-a-solo-coder/</guid>
      <description>I’ve spent the last couple years as a solo freelance developer. Comparing this experience to previously working in companies, I’ve noticed that those of us who work alone can have fewer iterative opportunities for improvement than developers who work on teams. Integral to having opportunities to improve is the concept of a short feedback loop: a process of incorporating new learning from observation and previous experience continuously over a short period of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Adorable bookmarklets want to help delete your social media data
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/adorable-bookmarklets-want-to-help-delete-your-social-media-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 13:12:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/adorable-bookmarklets-want-to-help-delete-your-social-media-data/</guid>
      <description>A little while ago I wrote about a Lambda function I called ephemeral for deleting my old tweets. While it’s a great project for someone familiar with or wanting to learn to use Lambda, it isn’t simple for a non-technical person to set up. There are services out there that will delete your tweets for you, but require your access credentials. There didn’t seem to be anything that provided convenience without also requiring authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            A coffee-break introduction to time complexity of algorithms
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/a-coffee-break-introduction-to-time-complexity-of-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 14:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/a-coffee-break-introduction-to-time-complexity-of-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>Just like writing your very first for loop, understanding time complexity is an integral milestone to learning how to write efficient complex programs. Think of it as having a superpower that allows you to know exactly what type of program might be the most efficient in a particular situation - before even running a single line of code.
The fundamental concepts of complexity analysis are well worth studying. You’ll be able to better understand how the code you’re writing will interact with the program’s input, and as a result, you’ll spend a lot less wasted time writing slow and problematic code.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Knapsack problem algorithms for my real-life carry-on knapsack
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/knapsack-problem-algorithms-for-my-real-life-carry-on-knapsack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 21:00:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/knapsack-problem-algorithms-for-my-real-life-carry-on-knapsack/</guid>
      <description>The knapsack problem I’m a nomad and live out of one carry-on bag. This means that the total weight of all my worldly possessions must fall under airline cabin baggage weight limits - usually 10kg. On some smaller airlines, however, this weight limit drops to 7kg. Occasionally, I have to decide not to bring something with me to adjust to the smaller weight limit.
As a practical exercise, deciding what to leave behind (or get rid of altogether) entails laying out all my things and choosing which ones to keep.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Why I&#39;m automatically deleting my old tweets using AWS Lambda
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/why-im-automatically-deleting-my-old-tweets-using-aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 10:51:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/why-im-automatically-deleting-my-old-tweets-using-aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>From now on, my tweets are ephemeral. Here’s why I’m deleting all my old tweets, and the AWS Lambda function I’m using to do all this for free.
Click here to skip to the code part.
Stuff and opinions I’ve only been a one-bag nomad for a little over a year and a half. Before that, I lived as most people do in an apartment or a house. I owned furniture, more clothing than I strictly needed, and enough “stuff” to fill at least a few moving boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Running a free Twitter bot on AWS Lambda
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/running-a-free-twitter-bot-on-aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 10:29:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/running-a-free-twitter-bot-on-aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>If you read About time, you’ll know that I’m a big believer in spending time now on building things that save time in the future. To this end I built a simple Twitter bot in Go that would occasionally post links to my articles and keep my account interesting even when I’m too busy to use it. The tweets help drive traffic to my sites, and I don’t have to lift a finger.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Moving to a new domain without breaking old links with AWS &amp; Disqus
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/moving-to-a-new-domain-without-breaking-old-links-with-aws-disqus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 08:56:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/moving-to-a-new-domain-without-breaking-old-links-with-aws-disqus/</guid>
      <description>I started blogging about my nomadic travels last year, and so far the habit has stuck. Like all side projects, I won’t typically invest heavily in setting up web properties before I can be reasonably certain that such an investment is worth my time or enjoyment. In other words: don’t buy the domain until you’ve proven to yourself that you’ll stick with it!
After some months of regular posting I felt I was ready to commit (short courtship, I know, but we’re all adults here) and I bought a dedicated domain, herOneBag.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            A Unicode substitution cipher algorithm
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/a-unicode-substitution-cipher-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 20:00:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/a-unicode-substitution-cipher-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>Full transparency: I occasionally waste time messing around on Twitter. (Gasp! Shock!) One of the ways I waste time messing around on Twitter is by writing my name in my profile with different Unicode character “fonts,” 𝖑𝖎𝖐𝖊 𝖙𝖍𝖎𝖘 𝖔𝖓𝖊. I previously did this by searching for different Unicode characters on Google, then one-by-one copying and pasting them into the “Name” field on my Twitter profile. Since this method of wasting time was a bit of a time waster, I decided (in true programmer fashion) to write a tool that would help me save some time while wasting it.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Hosting your static site with AWS S3, Route 53, and CloudFront
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/hosting-your-static-site-with-aws-s3-route-53-and-cloudfront/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 20:46:12 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/hosting-your-static-site-with-aws-s3-route-53-and-cloudfront/</guid>
      <description>Some time ago I decided to stop freeloading on GitHub pages and move one of my sites to Amazon Web Services (AWS). It turns out that I’m still mostly freeloading (yay free tier) so it amounted to a learning experience. Here are the components that let me host and serve the site at my custom domain with HTTPS.
 Static site in Amazon Web Services S3 bucket Route 53 handling the DNS CloudFront for distribution and a custom SSL certificate  I set all that up most of a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            About time
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/about-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 14:05:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/about-time/</guid>
      <description>This morning I read an article that’s been making the rounds lately: Modern Media Is a DoS Attack on Your Free Will.
It’s made me think, which I must admit, I at first didn’t like. See, when I wake up in the morning (and subsequently wake up my computer) the first thing I do is go on Twitter to catch up on everything I missed while I was asleep. All this before my first coffee, mind you.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Batch renaming images, including image resolution, with awk
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/batch-renaming-images-including-image-resolution-with-awk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 13:59:30 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/batch-renaming-images-including-image-resolution-with-awk/</guid>
      <description>The most recent item on my list of “Geeky things I did that made me feel pretty awesome” is an hour’s adventure that culminated in this code:
$ file IMG* | awk &#39;BEGIN{a=0} {print substr($1, 1, length($1)-5),a&#43;&#43;&#34;_&#34;substr($8,1, length($8)-1)}&#39; | while read fn fr; do echo $(rename -v &#34;s/$fn/img_$fr/g&#34; *); done IMG_20170808_172653_425.jpg renamed as img_0_4032x3024.jpg IMG_20170808_173020_267.jpg renamed as img_1_3024x3506.jpg IMG_20170808_173130_616.jpg renamed as img_2_3024x3779.jpg IMG_20170808_173221_425.jpg renamed as img_3_3024x3780.jpg IMG_20170808_173417_059.jpg renamed as img_4_2956x2980.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            How to code a satellite algorithm and cook paella from scratch
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-to-code-a-satellite-algorithm-and-cook-paella-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 16:50:24 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-to-code-a-satellite-algorithm-and-cook-paella-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>What if I told you that by the end of this article, you’ll be able to calculate the orbital period of satellites around Earth using their average altitudes and… You tuned out already, didn’t you?
Okay, how about this: I’m going to teach you how to make paella!
And you’ll have written a function that does the stuff I mentioned above, just like I did for this freeCodeCamp challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Making sandwiches with closures in JavaScript
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/making-sandwiches-with-closures-in-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 09:16:35 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/making-sandwiches-with-closures-in-javascript/</guid>
      <description>Say you’re having a little coding get-together, and you need some sandwiches. You happen to know that everyone prefers a different type of sandwich, like chicken, ham, or peanut butter and mayo. You could make all these sandwiches yourself, but that would be tedious and boring.
Luckily, you know of a nearby sandwich shop that delivers. They have the ability and ingredients to make any kind of sandwich in the world, and all you have to do is order through their app.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Understanding Array.prototype.reduce() and recursion using apple pie
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/understanding-array-prototype-reduce-and-recursion-using-apple-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 11:40:06 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/understanding-array-prototype-reduce-and-recursion-using-apple-pie/</guid>
      <description>I was having trouble understanding reduce() and recursion in JavaScript, so I wrote this article to explain it to myself (hey, look, recursion!). I hope you find my examples both helpful and delicious.
Given an array with nested arrays:
var arr = [1, [2], [3, [[4]]]]  We want to produce this:
var flat = [1, 2, 3, 4]  Using for loops and if statements Naively, if we know the maximum number of nested arrays we’ll encounter (there are 4 in this example), we can use for loops to iterate through each array item, then if statements to check if each item is in itself an array, and so on…</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Iterating over objects and arrays: frequent errors
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/iterating-over-objects-and-arrays-frequent-errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 10:46:46 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/iterating-over-objects-and-arrays-frequent-errors/</guid>
      <description>Here’s some complaining a quick overview of some code that has confounded me more than once. I’m told even very experienced developers encounter these situations regularly, so if you find yourself on your third cup of coffee scratching your head over why your code is doing exactly what you told it to do (and not what you want it to do), maybe this post can help you.
The example code is JavaScript, since that’s what I’ve been working in lately, but I believe the concepts to be pretty universal.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            How to replace a string in a dozen old blog posts with one sed terminal command
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-to-replace-a-string-in-a-dozen-old-blog-posts-with-one-sed-terminal-command/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 20:04:53 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-to-replace-a-string-in-a-dozen-old-blog-posts-with-one-sed-terminal-command/</guid>
      <description>June 1, 2018: This post was previously titled “That time 30 seconds, StackOverflow, and sed saved me 30 minutes” and has since been revised and updated with more examples and a couple new doodles. It’s better now.
I’ve had more than a few usernames, URLs, and Twitter handles over the years. Whether it was changing to something that better reflected my current interests or briefly getting caught up in the “.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Top free resources for developing coding superpowers
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/top-free-resources-for-developing-coding-superpowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 08:14:09 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/top-free-resources-for-developing-coding-superpowers/</guid>
      <description>I’m frequently asked for my opinion on how to get started on being a freelance developer. If you’re hoping to live the life of a remote working digital nomad, whichever career you choose, having a little coding expertise in your back pocket will be a big benefit.
Here’s a quick list of resources that you should definitely look at first if you’re hoping to gain some coding superpowers for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Things you need to know about becoming a Data Scientist
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/things-you-need-to-know-about-becoming-a-data-scientist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 13:19:19 +0900</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/things-you-need-to-know-about-becoming-a-data-scientist/</guid>
      <description>I recently attended a panel discussion hosted by General Assembly in Singapore entitled, “So you want to be a Data Scientist/Analyst”. The panel featured professionals in different stages of their careers and offered a wealth of information to an audience of hopefuls, including tips on how to land a job as a data scientist, and stories debunking myths that color this field.
The panelists Misrab Faizullah-Khan - VP of Data Science, GO_JEK</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            How I turned Unity into a tiling window manager
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-turned-unity-into-a-tiling-window-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 16:10:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-turned-unity-into-a-tiling-window-manager/</guid>
      <description>After a long and loving battle experience using i3 as my workhorse window manager on my old laptop, I’ve decided to mainly use Unity on my new laptop instead. I’m a huge fan of tiling window managers as a result of my i3 experience, however, the time it took to configure everything is longer than I wanted to spend getting set up before getting to work with my new laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            How I set up a single Dropbox folder on my dual-boot Windows and Linux system
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-set-up-a-single-dropbox-folder-on-my-dual-boot-windows-and-linux-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 10:58:01 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-set-up-a-single-dropbox-folder-on-my-dual-boot-windows-and-linux-system/</guid>
      <description>June 14, 2018: Ben Newhouse, former head of Sync at Dropbox, was kind enough to inform me that this set up might have unintended ill effects on your Dropbox data:
 Dropbox on Windows and Linux maintain metadata on each OS differently, so they’ll confuse each other. This will likely break things like version tracking and comments and as this isn’t a supported configuration probably worse.
 I’ve personally moved away from using Dropbox (and for that matter, dual-boot) since writing this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            How I created custom desktop notifications using terminal and cron
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-created-custom-desktop-notifications-using-terminal-and-cron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 10:48:38 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-created-custom-desktop-notifications-using-terminal-and-cron/</guid>
      <description>In my last post I talked about moving from Windows 10 to running i3 on Linux, built up from Debian Base System. Among other things, this change has taught me about the benefits of using basic tools and running a minimal, lightweight system. You can achieve a lot of functionality with just command line tools and simple utilities. One example I’d like to illustrate in this post is setting up desktop notifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            How a lifelong Windows user switched to Linux... the hard way
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-a-lifelong-windows-user-switched-to-linux-the-hard-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 14:23:59 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-a-lifelong-windows-user-switched-to-linux-the-hard-way/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let me preface this by saying that I’ve always been interested in finding out how things work. If a thing does something, I want to know why, how, and if I can customize it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It should come as no surprise that Windows 10 drove me crazy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            How I ditched WordPress and set up my custom domain HTTPS site for (almost) free
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-ditched-wordpress-and-set-up-my-custom-domain-https-site-for-almost-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 13:16:17 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/how-i-ditched-wordpress-and-set-up-my-custom-domain-https-site-for-almost-free/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got annoyed with WordPress.com. While using the service has its pros (like https and a mobile responsive website, and being very visual and beginner-friendly) it’s limiting. For someone who’s comfortable enough to be tweaking CSS but who’s not interested in creating their own theme (or paying upwards of $50 for one), I felt I wasn’t really the type of consumer WordPress.com was suited to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            Iterations in Python: for loop, list comprehension, and map
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/iterations-in-python-for-loop-list-comprehension-and-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 21:58:28 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/iterations-in-python-for-loop-list-comprehension-and-map/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been working in Python 3 for about a week, and so far greatly enjoy it. To me, learning code syntax (and programming in general) amounts to an amalgamation of lego blocks: once it’s understood what a certain color of block does, it’s straightforward to combine them to create the structure you’re looking for.
That said, some blocks can be a little confusing at first. I found documentation relating to iteration in Python to be a little hard to digest, mostly because of subtle differences in terminology: iteration, iterator, iterating, iterable… it’s enough to make your eyes glaze over.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
            The basics of streaming with Twitter API
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/the-basics-of-streaming-with-twitter-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 16:39:29 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/the-basics-of-streaming-with-twitter-api/</guid>
      <description>This post covers my initial adventures in exploring Twitter’s Streaming API. I’ll talk about:
 Getting started making a Twitter Streaming program using a template Problems arising from programming in Python with Windows 10 and Unicode Refining the search function  You can follow along with my template on Github.
1. Getting started If you’re new to Twitter’s Streaming API like I was this morning, here it is from the top.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>