<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Theme on VickyLai.io</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.io/tags/theme/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Theme on VickyLai.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 11:25:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://vickylai.io/tags/theme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            Moving to a new domain without breaking old links: AWS &amp; Disqus
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-new-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 08:56:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-new-domain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I started blogging about my nomadic travels last year, and so far the habit has stuck. Like all side projects, I won&amp;rsquo;t typically invest heavily in setting up web properties before I can be reasonably certain that such an investment is worth my time or enjoyment. In other words: don&amp;rsquo;t buy the domain until you&amp;rsquo;ve proven to yourself that you&amp;rsquo;ll stick with it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            A unicode substitution cipher algorithm
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/unicode-cipher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 20:00:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/unicode-cipher/</guid>
      <description>Full transparency: I occasionally waste time messing around on Twitter. (Gasp! Shock!) One of the ways I waste time messing around on Twitter is by writing my name in my profile with different unicode character &amp;ldquo;fonts,&amp;rdquo; 𝖑𝖎𝖐𝖊 𝖙𝖍𝖎𝖘 𝖔𝖓𝖊. I previously did this by searching for different unicode characters on Google, then one-by-one copying and pasting them into the &amp;ldquo;Name&amp;rdquo; field on my Twitter profile. Since this method of wasting time was a bit of a time waster, I decided (in true programmer fashion) to write a tool that would help me save some time while wasting it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            Hosting your static site with AWS S3, Route 53, and CloudFront
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 20:46:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-static-site/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some time ago I decided to stop freeloading on GitHub pages and move my static page for &lt;a href=&#34;https://vickylai.com&#34;&gt;vickylai.com&lt;/a&gt; to Amazon Web Services (AWS). It turns out that I&amp;rsquo;m still mostly freeloading (yay free tier) so it amounted to a learning experience. Here are the components that let me host and serve the site at my custom domain with HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            About time
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/about-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 14:05:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/about-time/</guid>
      <description>This morning I read an article that&amp;rsquo;s been making the rounds lately: Modern Media Is a DoS Attack on Your Free Will.
It&amp;rsquo;s made me think, which I must admit, I at first didn&amp;rsquo;t like. See, when I wake up in the morning (and subsequently wake up my computer) the first thing I do is go on Twitter to catch up on everything I missed while I was asleep. All this before my first coffee, mind you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            Batch renaming images, including image resolution, with awk
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/renaming-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 13:59:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/renaming-images/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The most recent item on my list of &amp;ldquo;Geeky things I did that made me feel pretty awesome&amp;rdquo; is an hour&amp;rsquo;s adventure that culminated in this code:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            How to code a satellite algorithm and cook paella from scratch
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/build-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 16:50:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/build-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>What if I told you that by the end of this article, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to calculate the orbital period of satellites around Earth using their average altitudes and&amp;hellip; You tuned out already, didn&amp;rsquo;t you?
Okay, how about this: I&amp;rsquo;m going to teach you how to make paella!
And you&amp;rsquo;ll have written a function that does the stuff I mentioned above, just like I did for this freeCodeCamp challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            Making sandwiches with closures in JavaScript
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/javascript-closures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 09:16:35 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/javascript-closures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Say you&amp;rsquo;re having a little coding get-together, and you need some sandwiches. You happen to know that everyone prefers a different type of sandwich, like chicken, ham, or peanut butter and mayo. You could make all these sandwiches yourself, but that would be tedious and boring.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            Understanding Array.prototype.reduce() and recursion using apple pie
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/reduce-recursion-with-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 11:40:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/reduce-recursion-with-pie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was having trouble understanding &lt;code&gt;reduce()&lt;/code&gt; and recursion in JavaScript, so I wrote this article to explain it to myself (hey, look, recursion!). I hope you find my examples both helpful and delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given an array with nested arrays:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            Iterating over objects and arrays: frequent errors
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/iterating-objects-arrays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 10:46:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/iterating-objects-arrays/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some complaining a quick overview of some code that has confounded me more than once. I&amp;rsquo;m told even very experienced developers encounter these situations regularly, so if you find yourself on your third cup of coffee scratching your head over why your code is doing exactly what you told it to do (and not what you want it to do), maybe this post can help you.
The example code is JavaScript, since that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ve been working in lately, but I believe the concepts to be pretty universal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            That time 30 seconds, StackOverflow, and sed saved me 30 minutes
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/when-stackoverflow-sed-saves-30mins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 20:04:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/when-stackoverflow-sed-saves-30mins/</guid>
      <description>This week, I launched my new website and changed my Twitter username to match. I was about to spend time going through all my old blog posts to find and update the URLs when this very future blog post popped up on my screen like Clippy and shook its pixelated head disapprovingly.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a worthwhile new habit for you: anytime you find yourself going &amp;ldquo;Ughhh I have to do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            Top free resources for developing coding superpowers
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-resources-for-coding-superpowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 08:14:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-resources-for-coding-superpowers/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m frequently asked for my opinion on how to get started on being a freelance developer. If you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to live the life of a remote working digital nomad, whichever career you choose, having a little coding expertise in your back pocket will be a big benefit.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick list of resources that you should definitely look at first if you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to gain some coding superpowers for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            Things you need to know about becoming a Data Scientist
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/to-be-a-data-scientist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 13:19:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/to-be-a-data-scientist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently attended a panel discussion hosted by General Assembly in Singapore entitled, &amp;ldquo;So you want to be a Data Scientist/Analyst&amp;rdquo;. The panel featured professionals in different stages of their careers and offered a wealth of information to an audience of hopefuls, including tips on how to land a job as a data scientist, and stories debunking myths that color this field. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            How I turned Unity into a tiling window manager
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/turn-unity-into-tiling-windows-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 16:10:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/turn-unity-into-tiling-windows-manager/</guid>
      <description>After a long and loving battle experience using i3 as my workhorse window manager on my old laptop, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to mainly use Unity on my new laptop instead. I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of tiling window managers as a result of my i3 experience, however, the time it took to configure everything is longer than I wanted to spend getting set up before getting to work with my new laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            How I set up a single Dropbox folder on my dual-boot Windows and Linux system
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/same-dropbox-dual-boot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 10:58:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/same-dropbox-dual-boot/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve now set up two different laptops to dual-boot Windows 10 and different Linux distributions. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to ensure you maintain one Dropbox folder over both operating systems.
Assuming Windows was there first:
 Mount the Windows drive in Linux Install Dropbox in Linux Sign in to link to Dropbox Immediately change Dropbox folder location to the mounted drive (same Dropbox folder as Windows)  Get it right the first time Dropbox will automatically set up your Dropbox folder when you run it the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>
        
            How I created custom desktop notifications using terminal and cron
        
      </title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/create-desktop-notifications-cron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 10:48:38 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/create-desktop-notifications-cron/</guid>
      <description>In my last post I talked about moving from Windows 10 to running i3 on Linux, built up from Debian Base System. Among other things, this change has taught me about the benefits of using basic tools and running a minimal, lightweight system. You can achieve a lot of functionality with just command line tools and simple utilities. One example I&amp;rsquo;d like to illustrate in this post is setting up desktop notifications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
