<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nerdy on VickyLai.io</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.com/tags/nerdy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nerdy on VickyLai.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 20:00:28 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vickylai.com/tags/nerdy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A unicode substitution cipher algorithm</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/unicode-cipher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2018 20:00:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/unicode-cipher/</guid>
      <description>Full transparency: I occasionally waste time messing around on Twitter. (Gasp! Shock!) One of the ways I waste time messing around on Twitter is by writing my name in my profile with different unicode character &amp;ldquo;fonts,&amp;rdquo; 𝖑𝖎𝖐𝖊 𝖙𝖍𝖎𝖘 𝖔𝖓𝖊. I previously did this by searching for different unicode characters on Google, then one-by-one copying and pasting them into the &amp;ldquo;Name&amp;rdquo; field on my Twitter profile. Since this method of wasting time was a bit of a time waster, I decided (in true programmer fashion) to write a tool that would help me save some time while wasting it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batch renaming images, including image resolution, with awk</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/renaming-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 13:59:30 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/renaming-images/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The most recent item on my list of &amp;ldquo;Geeky things I did that made me feel pretty awesome&amp;rdquo; is an hour&amp;rsquo;s adventure that culminated in this code:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I turned Unity into a tiling window manager</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/turn-unity-into-tiling-windows-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 16:10:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/turn-unity-into-tiling-windows-manager/</guid>
      <description>After a long and loving battle experience using i3 as my workhorse window manager on my old laptop, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to mainly use Unity on my new laptop instead. I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of tiling window managers as a result of my i3 experience, however, the time it took to configure everything is longer than I wanted to spend getting set up before getting to work with my new laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I created custom desktop notifications using terminal and cron</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/create-desktop-notifications-cron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 10:48:38 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/create-desktop-notifications-cron/</guid>
      <description>In my last post I talked about moving from Windows 10 to running i3 on Linux, built up from Debian Base System. Among other things, this change has taught me about the benefits of using basic tools and running a minimal, lightweight system. You can achieve a lot of functionality with just command line tools and simple utilities. One example I&amp;rsquo;d like to illustrate in this post is setting up desktop notifications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>