<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coding on VickyLai.io</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.io/tags/coding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coding on VickyLai.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 16:50:24 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vickylai.io/tags/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a program, or make dinner, from scratch</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/20170908-build-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 16:50:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/20170908-build-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What if I told you that by the end of this article, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to calculate the orbital period of satellites around Earth using their average altitudes and&amp;hellip; You tuned out already, didn&amp;rsquo;t you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, how about this: I&amp;rsquo;m going to teach you how to make paella!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://vickylai.io/pixels/solve-paella.jpg#center&#34; alt=&#34;It&#39;s a paella party!&#34; /&gt;
&lt;p class=&#34;has-text-centered img-caption&#34;&gt;True fact: people are far more likely to accept complexity if it comes with the promise of food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making sandwiches with closures in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/javascript-closures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 09:16:35 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/javascript-closures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://vickylai.io/pixels/closures-sandwich.jpg#center&#34; alt=&#34;Peanut butter and mayo sandwich.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Say you&amp;rsquo;re having a little coding get-together, and you need some sandwiches. You happen to know that everyone prefers a different type of sandwich, like chicken, ham, or peanut butter and mayo. You could make all these sandwiches yourself, but that would be tedious and boring.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Array.prototype.reduce() and recursion using apple pie</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/reduce-recursion-with-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 11:40:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/reduce-recursion-with-pie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://vickylai.io/pixels/recursion-pie.jpg#center&#34; alt=&#34;Delicious attention-retaining recursion pie.&#34; /&gt;
&lt;p class=&#34;has-text-centered img-caption&#34;&gt;Delicious, attention-retaining recursion pie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was having trouble understanding &lt;code&gt;reduce()&lt;/code&gt; and recursion in JavaScript, so I wrote this article to explain it to myself (hey, look, recursion!). I hope you find my examples both helpful and delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given an array with nested arrays:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iterating over objects and arrays: frequent errors</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/iterating-objects-arrays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 10:46:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/iterating-objects-arrays/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some complaining a quick overview of some code that has confounded me more than once. I&amp;rsquo;m told even very experienced developers encounter these situations regularly, so if you find yourself on your third cup of coffee scratching your head over why your code is doing exactly what you told it to do (and not what you want it to do), maybe this post can help you.
The example code is JavaScript, since that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ve been working in lately, but I believe the concepts to be pretty universal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That time 30 seconds, StackOverflow, and sed saved me 30 minutes</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/when-stackoverflow-sed-saves-30mins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 20:04:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/when-stackoverflow-sed-saves-30mins/</guid>
      <description>This week, I launched my new website and changed my Twitter username to match. I was about to spend time going through all my old blog posts to find and update the URLs when this very future blog post popped up on my screen like Clippy and shook its pixelated head disapprovingly.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a worthwhile new habit for you: anytime you find yourself going &amp;ldquo;Ughhh I have to do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top free resources for developing coding superpowers</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-resources-for-coding-superpowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 08:14:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-resources-for-coding-superpowers/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m frequently asked for my opinion on how to get started on being a freelance developer. If you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to live the life of a remote working digital nomad, whichever career you choose, having a little coding expertise in your back pocket will be a big benefit.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick list of resources that you should definitely look at first if you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to gain some coding superpowers for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of programming: iterations in Python</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/python-programming-fundamentals-iterations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 21:58:28 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/python-programming-fundamentals-iterations/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working in Python 3 for about a week, and so far greatly enjoy it. To me, learning code syntax (and programming in general) amounts to an amalgamation of lego blocks: once it&amp;rsquo;s understood what a certain color of block does, it&amp;rsquo;s straightforward to combine them to create the structure you&amp;rsquo;re looking for.
That said, some blocks can be a little confusing at first. I found documentation relating to iteration in Python to be a little hard to digest, mostly because of subtle differences in terminology: iteration, iterator, iterating, iterable&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s enough to make your eyes glaze over.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>