<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media on VickyLai.com</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.com/tags/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media on VickyLai.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 13:12:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vickylai.com/tags/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adorable bookmarklets want to help delete your social media data</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/bookmarklets-delete-social-media-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 13:12:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/bookmarklets-delete-social-media-data/</guid>
      <description>A little while ago I wrote about a Lambda function I called ephemeral for deleting my old tweets. While it&amp;rsquo;s a great project for someone familiar with or wanting to learn to use Lambda, it isn&amp;rsquo;t simple for a non-technical person to set up. There are services out there that will delete your tweets for you, but require your access credentials. There didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be anything that provided convenience without also requiring authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m automatically deleting my old tweets using AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/delete-old-tweets-ephemeral/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 10:51:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/delete-old-tweets-ephemeral/</guid>
      <description>From now on, my tweets are ephemeral. Here’s why I’m deleting all my old tweets, and the AWS Lambda function I’m using to do all this for free.
Click here to skip to the code part.
Stuff and opinions I&amp;rsquo;ve only been a one-bag nomad for a little over a year and a half. Before that, I lived as most people do in an apartment or a house. I owned furniture, more clothing than I strictly needed, and enough &amp;ldquo;stuff&amp;rdquo; to fill at least a few moving boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About time</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/about-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 14:05:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/about-time/</guid>
      <description>This morning I read an article that&amp;rsquo;s been making the rounds lately: Modern Media Is a DoS Attack on Your Free Will.
It&amp;rsquo;s made me think, which I must admit, I at first didn&amp;rsquo;t like. See, when I wake up in the morning (and subsequently wake up my computer) the first thing I do is go on Twitter to catch up on everything I missed while I was asleep. All this before my first coffee, mind you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>