<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Go on VickyLai.com</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.com/tags/go/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Go on VickyLai.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 21:00:35 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vickylai.com/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Knapsack problem algorithms for my real-life carry-on knapsack</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/knapsack-go-approaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 21:00:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/knapsack-go-approaches/</guid>
      <description>The knapsack problem I&amp;rsquo;m a nomad and live out of one carry-on bag. This means that the total weight of all my worldly possessions must fall under airline cabin baggage weight limits - usually 10kg. On some smaller airlines, however, this weight limit drops to 7kg. Occasionally, I have to decide not to bring something with me to adjust to the smaller weight limit.
As a practical exercise, deciding what to leave behind (or get rid of altogether) entails laying out all my things and choosing which ones to keep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m automatically deleting my old tweets using AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/delete-old-tweets-ephemeral/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 10:51:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/delete-old-tweets-ephemeral/</guid>
      <description>From now on, my tweets are ephemeral. Here’s why I’m deleting all my old tweets, and the AWS Lambda function I’m using to do all this for free.
Click here to skip to the code part.
Stuff and opinions I&amp;rsquo;ve only been a one-bag nomad for a little over a year and a half. Before that, I lived as most people do in an apartment or a house. I owned furniture, more clothing than I strictly needed, and enough &amp;ldquo;stuff&amp;rdquo; to fill at least a few moving boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running a free Twitter bot on AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/free-twitter-bot-aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 10:29:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/free-twitter-bot-aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>If you read About time, you&amp;rsquo;ll know that I&amp;rsquo;m a big believer in spending time now on building things that save time in the future. To this end I built a simple Twitter bot in Go that would occasionally post links to my articles and keep my account interesting even when I&amp;rsquo;m too busy to use it. The tweets help drive traffic to my sites, and I don&amp;rsquo;t have to lift a finger.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>