<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Time Saver on VickyLai.com</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.com/tags/time-saver/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Time Saver on VickyLai.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 10:51:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vickylai.com/tags/time-saver/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m automatically deleting my old tweets using AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/delete-old-tweets-ephemeral/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 10:51:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/delete-old-tweets-ephemeral/</guid>
      <description>From now on, my tweets are ephemeral. Here&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m deleting all my old tweets and the AWS Lambda function that does it for free.
Click here to skip to the code part.
Stuff and opinions I&amp;rsquo;ve only been a one-bag nomad for a little over a year and a half. Before that, I lived as most people do in an apartment or a house. I owned furniture, more clothing than I strictly needed, and enough &amp;ldquo;stuff&amp;rdquo; to fill at least a few moving boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About time</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/about-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 14:05:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/about-time/</guid>
      <description>This morning I read an article that&amp;rsquo;s been making the rounds lately: Modern Media Is a DoS Attack on Your Free Will.
It&amp;rsquo;s made me think, which I must admit, I at first didn&amp;rsquo;t like. See, when I wake up in the morning (and subsequently wake up my computer) the first thing I do is go on Twitter to catch up on everything I missed while I was asleep. All this before my first coffee, mind you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batch renaming images, including image resolution, with awk</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/renaming-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 13:59:30 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/renaming-images/</guid>
      <description>The most recent item on my list of &amp;ldquo;Geeky things I did that made me feel pretty awesome&amp;rdquo; is an hour&amp;rsquo;s adventure that culminated in this code:
$ file IMG* | awk &#39;BEGIN{a=0} {print substr($1, 1, length($1)-5),a++&amp;quot;_&amp;quot;substr($8,1, length($8)-1)}&#39; | while read fn fr; do echo $(rename -v &amp;quot;s/$fn/img_$fr/g&amp;quot; *); done IMG_20170808_172653_425.jpg renamed as img_0_4032x3024.jpg IMG_20170808_173020_267.jpg renamed as img_1_3024x3506.jpg IMG_20170808_173130_616.jpg renamed as img_2_3024x3779.jpg IMG_20170808_173221_425.jpg renamed as img_3_3024x3780.jpg IMG_20170808_173417_059.jpg renamed as img_4_2956x2980.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That time 30 seconds, StackOverflow, and sed saved me 30 minutes</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/when-stackoverflow-sed-saves-30mins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 20:04:53 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/when-stackoverflow-sed-saves-30mins/</guid>
      <description>This week, I launched my new website and changed my Twitter username to match. I was about to spend time going through all my old blog posts to find and update the URLs when this very future blog post popped up on my screen like Clippy and shook its pixelated head disapprovingly.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a worthwhile new habit for you: anytime you find yourself going &amp;ldquo;Ughhh I have to do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I created custom desktop notifications using terminal and cron</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.com/verbose/create-desktop-notifications-cron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 10:48:38 +0700</pubDate>
      <author>hello@vickylai.com (Vicky Lai)</author>
      <guid>https://vickylai.com/verbose/create-desktop-notifications-cron/</guid>
      <description>In my last post I talked about moving from Windows 10 to running i3 on Linux, built up from Debian Base System. Among other things, this change has taught me about the benefits of using basic tools and running a minimal, lightweight system. You can achieve a lot of functionality with just command line tools and simple utilities. One example I&amp;rsquo;d like to illustrate in this post is setting up desktop notifications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>