<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Backend on VickyLai.io</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.io/tags/backend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Backend on VickyLai.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 20:46:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vickylai.io/tags/backend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting your static site with AWS S3, Route 53, and CloudFront</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 20:46:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-static-site/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some time ago I decided to stop freeloading on GitHub pages and move my static page for &lt;a href=&#34;https://vickylai.com&#34;&gt;vickylai.com&lt;/a&gt; to Amazon Web Services (AWS). It turns out that I&amp;rsquo;m still mostly freeloading (yay free tier) so it amounted to a learning experience. Here are the components that let me host and serve the site at my custom domain with HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batch renaming images, including image resolution, with awk</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/renaming-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 13:59:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/renaming-images/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The most recent item on my list of &amp;ldquo;Geeky things I did that made me feel pretty awesome&amp;rdquo; is an hour&amp;rsquo;s adventure that culminated in this code:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making sandwiches with closures in JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/javascript-closures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2017 09:16:35 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/javascript-closures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Say you&amp;rsquo;re having a little coding get-together, and you need some sandwiches. You happen to know that everyone prefers a different type of sandwich, like chicken, ham, or peanut butter and mayo. You could make all these sandwiches yourself, but that would be tedious and boring.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Array.prototype.reduce() and recursion using apple pie</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/reduce-recursion-with-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 11:40:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/reduce-recursion-with-pie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was having trouble understanding &lt;code&gt;reduce()&lt;/code&gt; and recursion in JavaScript, so I wrote this article to explain it to myself (hey, look, recursion!). I hope you find my examples both helpful and delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given an array with nested arrays:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iterating over objects and arrays: frequent errors</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/iterating-objects-arrays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 10:46:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/iterating-objects-arrays/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some complaining a quick overview of some code that has confounded me more than once. I&amp;rsquo;m told even very experienced developers encounter these situations regularly, so if you find yourself on your third cup of coffee scratching your head over why your code is doing exactly what you told it to do (and not what you want it to do), maybe this post can help you.
The example code is JavaScript, since that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ve been working in lately, but I believe the concepts to be pretty universal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top free resources for developing coding superpowers</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-resources-for-coding-superpowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 08:14:09 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/free-resources-for-coding-superpowers/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m frequently asked for my opinion on how to get started on being a freelance developer. If you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to live the life of a remote working digital nomad, whichever career you choose, having a little coding expertise in your back pocket will be a big benefit.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick list of resources that you should definitely look at first if you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to gain some coding superpowers for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve been a back-end coder for a week: here&#39;s how I made a Twitter stream</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/how-i-made-a-twitter-stream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 16:39:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/how-i-made-a-twitter-stream/</guid>
      <description>This post covers my initial adventures in exploring Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Streaming API. I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about:
 Getting started making a Twitter Streaming program using a template Problems arising from programming in Python with Windows 10 and Unicode Refining the search function  You can follow along with my template on Github.
1. Getting started If you&amp;rsquo;re new to Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Streaming API like I was this morning, here it is from the top.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>