<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aws on VickyLai.io</title>
    <link>https://vickylai.io/tags/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aws on VickyLai.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 10:29:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vickylai.io/tags/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Running a free Twitter bot on AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-lambda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 10:29:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-lambda/</guid>
      <description>If you read About time, you&amp;rsquo;ll know that I&amp;rsquo;m a big believer in spending time now on building things that save time in the future. To this end I built a simple Twitter bot in Go that would occasionally post links to my articles and keep my account interesting even when I&amp;rsquo;m too busy to use it. The tweets help drive traffic to my sites, and I don&amp;rsquo;t have to lift a finger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to a new domain without breaking old links: AWS &amp; Disqus</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-new-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 08:56:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-new-domain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I started blogging about my nomadic travels last year, and so far the habit has stuck. Like all side projects, I won&amp;rsquo;t typically invest heavily in setting up web properties before I can be reasonably certain that such an investment is worth my time or enjoyment. In other words: don&amp;rsquo;t buy the domain until you&amp;rsquo;ve proven to yourself that you&amp;rsquo;ll stick with it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting your static site with AWS S3, Route 53, and CloudFront</title>
      <link>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 20:46:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vickylai.io/verbose/aws-static-site/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some time ago I decided to stop freeloading on GitHub pages and move my static page for &lt;a href=&#34;https://vickylai.com&#34;&gt;vickylai.com&lt;/a&gt; to Amazon Web Services (AWS). It turns out that I&amp;rsquo;m still mostly freeloading (yay free tier) so it amounted to a learning experience. Here are the components that let me host and serve the site at my custom domain with HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>